Don't feed the animals.
Night of the Zoopocalypse is a animation, comedy,
horror film directed by Ricardo Curtis.
A wolf and mountain lion team up when a meteor unleashes a
virus turning zoo animals into zombies.
They join forces with other survivors to rescue the zoo and stop
the deranged mutant leader from spreading the virus.
Gracie (voice), played by Gabriella Kosmidis.
Dan (voice), played by David Harbour.
Xavier / Bill (voice), played by Pierre Simpson.
Felix (voice), played by Paul Sun-Hyung Lee.
Ash (voice), played by Scott Thompson.
Poot (voice), played by Christina Nova.
Night of the Zoopocalypse (originally titled as Night of the Zoombies) is a 2024 animated comedy horror film directed by storyboard artists Rodrigo Perez-Castro and Ricardo Curtis  (who also served as storyboard supervisors of the film while Perez-Castro
served as its design supervisor), written by James Kee and producer Steven Hoban; inspired by a concept by one of the film's executive producers and Hellraiser creator Clive Barker, loosely based on his unpublished short story "ZOOmbies".
The film follows a group of animal survivors in a zoo trying to survive a zombie outbreak when a
virus carried on a meteor turns various zoo creatures into slobbering mutant zombies.
It premiered at the 57th Sitges Film Festival on October 6, 2024, then being released in France by Apollo Films on January 29, 2025, Belgium on
February 19, 2025, and in the United States and Canada by Viva Kids and Elevation Pictures on March 7, 2025, receiving positive reviews.
The film explores themes of aftercreditsstinger,
horror for children, animated horror.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and thought_provoking.